Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Faculty files, 1946 -- 2018; UA252.005; 18 Linear Feet
  - Collier, Robert D., 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.020.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Collins, Michael F., 1987 -- 1996; UA252.005.020.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Collins, Sherwood, 1963 -- 2003; UA252.005.020.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 26)
    photos/newspaper clippings/bio sheets/obituary/project proposal/faculty news/personnel records
  - Colon, Melvyn, 1997 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Conklin, John, 1970 -- 1996; UA252.005.020.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 28)
    photos/newspaper clippings/bio sheet/academic paper/personnel record
  - Connolly, Barbara, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.020.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Cook, Robert, 1992 -- 2001; UA252.005.020.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Cook, Robert W., 1979 -- 1993; UA252.005.020.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 31)
    photos/newspaper clippings/diagram/curriculum vitae/bio sheet
  - Corcoran, Paul, 1985 -- 1986; UA252.005.020.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 32)
    photos/newspaper articles
  - Cormack, Alan M., 1962 -- 2000; UA252.005.020.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 33)
    photos/newspaper clippings/magazines/letters/personnel records/curriculum vitae/news transcripts/National Medal of Science program/obituary
  - Corwin, Michael, 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.020.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Couch, Alva, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.020.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Court, Michael, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.020.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Courtois, Veronique, 1992 -- 1997; UA252.005.020.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 37)
    biography paragraph
  - Covic, Lidija, 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.020.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Crane, Gregory, 1992 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Cronin, Kathe, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.020.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Cronin-Golomb, Mark, 1987 -- 1994; UA252.005.020.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Crochetiere, William, 1967 -- 1994; UA252.005.020.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 42)
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel records/faculty news/academic papers/letters
  - Cruz, Isabel, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.020.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 43)
    photos/article
  - Cukor, Peter, 1970 -- 2007; UA252.005.020.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Cotter, Susan, 1981 -- 1991; UA252.005.020.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Cruz, Gabriela Gomes da, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Dalang, Robert, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.020.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - d'Alarcao, Marc, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.020.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - d'Alton, Mary, 1997 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Damassa, David A., 1984 -- 1984; UA252.005.020.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 50)
    magazine article/curriculum vitae
  - Damoulis, Petros, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.020.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Dane, Benjamin, 1966 -- 1989; UA252.005.020.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 52)
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel record/curriculum vitae/award presentation
  - Daniels, Norman, 1971 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 53)
    photos/newspaper clippings/articles/letters/academic papers/grant award/bio sheet
  - Daost, Philip, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Dapice, David, 1975 -- 2002; UA252.005.020.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 55)
    photos/newspaper clippings/academic paper
  - Darzenta, Nicholas, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.020.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Dawson-Hughes, Bess, 1985 -- 2001; UA252.005.020.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 57)
    photos/newspaper clippings/CD/articles/news clip data sheet
  - Dayal, Yogeshwar, 1979 -- 1983; UA252.005.020.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 58)
    magazine clipping/academic paper
  - Debernardez-Clark, Eliana, 1989 -- 2001; UA252.005.020.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 59)
    photos/resume
  - Debold, Joe, 2003 -- 2003; UA252.005.020.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Delellis, Ronald A., 1980 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Dempsey, Peter, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Dennett, Daniel D., 1971 -- 2003; UA252.005.020.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 63)
    photos/newspaper clippings/event program/interview transcript/faculty profile/articles/letters/book reviews/academic paper/career narrative
  - Dente, Edmund, 1986 -- 1986; UA252.005.020.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Deranian, H Martin, 1985 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Der Manuelian, Lucy, 1981 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 66)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letters/articles/pamphlets/curriculum vitae/biography sheets
  - DesForges, Jane, 1983 -- 1993; UA252.005.020.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - DeVoto, Mark, 1982 -- 1986; UA252.005.020.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 68)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biographical data sheet
  - Dewald, Robert R., 1965 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 69)
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel record/introduction sheet
  - Dhupa, Nishi, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.020.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Diamond, Judith, 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.020.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Diamond, Norman, 1980 -- 2013; UA252.005.020.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - DiBiaggio, John (pt.2), 1992 -- 1998; UA252.005.020.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - DiBiaggio, John, 1988 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    photos/newspaper clippings/event program/bio/articles/letters/pamphlet
  - Dice, J. Fred, 1986 -- 2002; UA252.005.021.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dickman, Robert, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.021.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Digges, Deborah, 1987 -- 1996; UA252.005.021.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book jacket/article
  - Dietz, William, 1983 -- 1990; UA252.005.021.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Dillaway, Guy, 1986 -- 1987; UA252.005.021.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Dillon, Jeanne, 1980 -- 1987; UA252.005.021.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biographical data sheet/Curriculum Vitae
  - DiMasi, Joseph, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.021.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Dinarello, Charles, 1986 -- 1994; UA252.005.021.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae
  - Distasio, Gene, 1950 -- 1960; UA252.005.021.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - DiStasio, Joseph, 1983 -- 1989; UA252.005.021.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - DiStefano, Roseanne, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Dlhosh, Sharon, 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.021.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Dixon, Linda, 1992 -- 1993; UA252.005.021.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dobrow, Julie, 1996 -- 1998; UA252.005.021.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Dodman, Nicholas H., 1983 -- 1998; UA252.005.021.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 16)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book jacket
  - Dohner, Robert, 1983 -- 1986; UA252.005.021.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Doku, H. Chris, 1988 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Donnenfeld, Walter, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Doumanidis, Charalabos, 1994 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Downes, Thomas, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.021.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Drachman, Virginia, 1979 -- 2002; UA252.005.021.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 22)
    photos/article/letter/book jacket/biographical data sheet /magazine
  - Dunbar, Stuart, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Dunlap, Kathleen, 1983 -- 1988; UA252.005.021.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Dunn, John A., 1970 -- 1980; UA252.005.021.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 25)
    photos/newspaper clippings/resumes/academic paper/press releases/charts
  - Dunn, Kevin, 1995 -- 2002; UA252.005.021.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 26)
    photos/biographical blurb
  - Durant, John, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.021.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 27)
    letter
  - Dwyer, Joanna, 1980 -- 1999; UA252.005.021.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 28)
    photos/newspaper clippings/resume/speech
  - Easterbrooks, M. Anne, 1986 -- 1993; UA252.005.021.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Ebert, Karl, 1985 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Eckman, Mark, 1985 -- 1994; UA252.005.021.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Economos, Christina, 1999 -- 2005; UA252.005.021.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 32)
    photos/printed emails
  - Edelman, Lee, 1980 -- 1995; UA252.005.021.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Edgers, Lewis, 1967 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 34)
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel records
  - Eggleston, Karen, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Eichenberg, Richard, 1985 -- 1990; UA252.005.021.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 36)
    photos/newspaper clippings/resumes
  - El-Bermani, Al-Walid, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.021.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Elias, Robert, 1980 -- 1988; UA252.005.021.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 38)
    newspaper clippings/biographical data sheets
  - Elkind, David, 1979 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Elkind, David #1, 1978 -- 1994; UA252.005.021.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 40)
    photos/newspaper clippings/professional data sheet/resume/publications list/book release packet
  - Ellison, James, 1964 -- 1989; UA252.005.021.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 41)
    photos/newspaper clippings/retirement resolution/curriculum vitae/press releases/personnel record/sketches/faculty note
  - Ellmore, George S., 1980 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - El-Zein, Amira, 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.021.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Emerson, Sheila, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 44)
    press release
  - Emhoff, Timothy, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Engelking, Larry R., 1985 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 46)
    photo/curriculum vitae
  - England, Michael, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Ennis, James G., 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.021.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 48)
    newspaper clipping/curriculum vitae
  - Erickson, Jeffrey, 1985 -- 1988; UA252.005.021.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Erickson, Brian, 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.021.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Ernst, Susan G., 1983 -- 2000; UA252.005.021.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 51)
    photos/newspaper clippings/article
  - Estes, Mark, 1986 -- 1986; UA252.005.021.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Etish-Andrews, Jane, 1983 -- 1994; UA252.005.021.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Evans, Joseph, 1983 -- 1986; UA252.005.021.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 54)
    photos/newspaper clippings/resume
  - Everett, Allen E., 1963 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 55)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/faculty note/letters/personnel record
  - Everett, Bruce, 2003 -- 2003; UA252.005.021.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Fanburg, Barry, 1992 -- 1996; UA252.005.021.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Fantini, Sergio, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.021.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Fareau, Bob, 1987 -- 1993; UA252.005.021.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Fawaz, Leila, 1982 -- 2002; UA252.005.021.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 60)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biographical blurb/letters/curriculum vitae
  - Feinburg, Sylvia, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 61)
    article
  - Feingold, Murray, 1980 -- 1984; UA252.005.021.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Reldberg, Ross, 1976 -- 1990; UA252.005.021.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 63)
    photos/newspaper clippings/grant announcement
  - Feldman, David, 1979 -- 1998; UA252.005.021.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 64)
    photos/newspaper clippings/magazine/grant proposal/curriculum vitae
  - Femenias, Blenda, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 65)
    biography blurb
  - Fermental, Denis, 1968 -- 1984; UA252.005.021.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 66)
    photos/newspaper clippings/personnel record/faculty news
  - Fertitta, Luisa, 1983 -- 1986; UA252.005.021.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Feig, Larry, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Feigenbaum, Lenore, 1987 -- 1990; UA252.005.021.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Fiaterone, Maria, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.021.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Field, John Osgood, 1980 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Flax, Martin, 1995 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Floyd, Margaret H., 1979 -- 1992; UA252.005.021.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Flynn, Carol H., 1986 -- 1996; UA252.005.021.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Flynn, Robert E., 1986 -- 1991; UA252.005.021.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Flytzani-Stephanopolous, Maria, 1994 -- 2003; UA252.005.021.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Fogels, Helmi, 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.021.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Folstein, Marshal F., 1996 -- 2001; UA252.005.021.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Folstein, Susan, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.021.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Ford, Lawrence H., 1980 -- 1997; UA252.005.021.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Forgac, Michael D., 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.021.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Forgione, Albert, 1979 -- 2006; UA252.005.021.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Forrester, Janet, 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.021.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Fortune, Peter, 1980 -- 1991; UA252.005.021.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 84)
    photos/newspaper clippings/academic paper/magazine/curriculum vitae/biographical data sheet
  - Franceschini, Maria, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.021.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Francis, Sing-Chen Lydia, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.022.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Frankenstein, Laura, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.022.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Frantz, Ivan DeRay, 1985 -- 1993; UA252.005.022.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Freden, Greg, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.022.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Freeman, Lisa, 1997 -- 2002; UA252.005.022.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Freedman, Barbara, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.022.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 6)
    biographical blurb
  - Freeman, Richard, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.022.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Frisken, Sarah, 2005 -- 2005; UA252.005.022.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fuhrman, Juliet, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.022.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Furie, Barbara C., 1988 -- 1988; UA252.005.022.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Furie, Bruce, 1990 -- 1997; UA252.005.022.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Furkart, Audrey, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.022.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Fyler, John M., 1971 -- 1982; UA252.005.022.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 13)
    newspaper clippings/personnel record/fellowship proposal/biographical data sheet
  - Freundenreich, Catherine, 1999 -- 2002; UA252.005.022.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Gagari, Elani, 2000 -- 2002; UA252.005.022.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Galantic, Ivan, 1970 -- 1989; UA252.005.022.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 16)
    photos/newspaper articles/fact sheet/news release
  - Galburt, Roger (Dental), 1999-12 -- 1999-12; UA252.005.022.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Gallagher, James B. (Professor, Dentistry), 1987-08-10 -- 1987-08-10; UA252.005.022.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Galvin, John R. (Fletcher School), 1995-09 -- 1998-01-17; UA252.005.022.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Gans. Dr. Bruce (Medical School), 1987-08-12 -- 1987-08-12; UA252.005.022.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Garcia-Godoy, F. (Dental), 1990 -- 2005; UA252.005.022.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Garcia-Sellers, Martha Julia, 1997-10-21 -- 1998-11-24; UA252.005.022.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Gardulski, Anne F. (Liberal Arts), 1989-01 -- 1993-08; UA252.005.022.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Garman, David (Economics Dept), 1991-09 -- 1991-09; UA252.005.022.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Garvin, William (Medical), 1965 -- 2004; UA252.005.022.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Gasarian, Gerad (French), 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.022.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Gattoni-Celli, Dr. Sebastiano (Medical School), 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.022.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Gault, Dr. Barry W. (Medical School), 1990-05 -- 1990-05; UA252.005.022.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Gavel, Dr. Murray J. (Dental School), 1989 -- 1999-08-19; UA252.005.022.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Gean, Margaret (Medical School), 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.022.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Gehling, Bill (Athletics), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.022.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Gelfand, Dr. Jeffrey (Medical School), 1980-10-22 -- 1998-03-12; UA252.005.022.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Gellis, Dr. Sydney S. (Medical School), 1979-01-17 -- 1985-03-04; UA252.005.022.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Georgakis, Christos (Engineering), 2004-01 -- 2004-01; UA252.005.022.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Gershoff, Stanley (Nutrition), 1977-04-19 -- 2001; UA252.005.022.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Ghublikian, John (Chem. Engineering), 1989-09 -- 1989-09; UA252.005.022.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Gibson. John S. (Liberal Arts/PLY SCI), 1963-04-29 -- 1995-05; UA252.005.022.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Gidney, Calvin (Child Study), 1993-09 -- 2000-09; UA252.005.022.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Gilchrest, Dr. Barbara A. (Medical School), 1985-07-30 -- 1989; UA252.005.022.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Gilfillian, Dr. Robert (Veterinary School), 1983-10-10 -- 1987-07-31; UA252.005.022.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Gill, Gerald (Liberal Arts/History), 1980-10-22 -- 2012-10-17; UA252.005.022.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Gill, Dr. Michael (Medical School), 1983-01-01 -- 1988-09; UA252.005.022.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Ginsberg, Stephen J. (Dental School), 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.022.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Gittleman, Robyn, 1976-03-26 -- 1990; UA252.005.022.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Gittleman, Sol (Liberal Arts/Provost), 1964 -- 2004-10-29; UA252.005.022.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Giunta, Dr. John (Dental School), 1972-02-17 -- 1987-04-21; UA252.005.022.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Glassroth, Jeffrey (Medical), 2001-05 -- 2005-02-02; UA252.005.022.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Glater, Marilyn T. (Liberal Arts/Poly Sci), 1986-02-14 -- 1994; UA252.005.022.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Glaser, James (Political Science), 1983-11-02 -- 2004-08; UA252.005.022.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Glotzer, Ruth M. (Medical), 1997-12-04 -- 1998; UA252.005.022.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Glynn, Thomas P., 1980 -- 2018; UA252.005.022.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Goldberg, Jeanne (Medical School/HNRC), 1978-02 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Goldberg, Dr. Michael (Medical School), 1980-11-03 -- 1987-03-17; UA252.005.023.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Goldenberg, Dr. Don (Medical), 1989 -- 2016; UA252.005.023.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Goldin, Dr. Barry (Medical School), 1980-02-14 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Goldman, Dr. Melvin (Dental School), 1986-06-15 -- 1996-05-08; UA252.005.023.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Goldner, Ronald B. (Liberal Arts/Engineering), 1964-08-20 -- 1990-11; UA252.005.023.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Goldsmith, Michelle (Veterinary), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.023.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Goldstein, Gary R (Liberal Arts/Physics), 1969-06-05 -- 1986-02-20; UA252.005.023.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Golstein-Gelb, Warren (Enviroment), 1997-11-03 -- 1997-11-03; UA252.005.023.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Golebiowska, Ewa (Political Science), 1995 -- 1997; UA252.005.023.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Gomez, Gabriel (Liberal Arts), 1960 -- 1980; UA252.005.023.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Gonsalves, Robert A. (Liberal Arts/Electro OP), 1985-10-31 -- 2000-05; UA252.005.023.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Gontheir, Mark (Administration/Sum. SCH), 1986-10-09 -- 2001; UA252.005.023.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Gonzales, Fulton (Math department), 1990-09 -- 1990-09; UA252.005.023.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Goode, Robert K. (Dental), 1999-03-11 -- 1999-03-11; UA252.005.023.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Gorbach, Dr. Sherwood (Medical School), 1977-07-24 -- 2002; UA252.005.023.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Gordon, Dr. Phillip (Dental), 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.023.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Gouvia, William (Medical), 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Grand, Dr. Richard J. Grand (Medical), 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.023.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Granowitz, Eric (Medical), 1997 -- 1998; UA252.005.023.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Green, Martin B (Liberal Arts/English), 1967-01-10 -- 1993; UA252.005.023.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Greenblatt, Dr. David (Medical School), 1980-02-28 -- 1997-10; UA252.005.023.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Greenfield, Dr. Sheldon (Medical School), 1996 -- 1997; UA252.005.023.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Greif, Robert (Liberal Arts/Mech. Eng), 1966-10-27 -- 1987; UA252.005.023.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Grigoriev, Sergei, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.023.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Grossman, Barbara (Arts and Sciences), 1994-04 -- 1994-04; UA252.005.023.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Grossman, Dr. Jerome H. (Medical School), 1980-08-25 -- 1992; UA252.005.023.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Guertin, Margo (Electrical Eng.), 1999 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Guertin, Dean Robert P. (Liberal Arts), 1968 -- 1989; UA252.005.023.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Gunther, Loen (Liberal Arts/Physics), 1965-10-28 -- 1985-06-21; UA252.005.023.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Gurewich, Dr. Victor (Medical School), 1985-03 -- 1987-03-24; UA252.005.023.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Guss, David (Anthropology), 2003 -- 2003; UA252.005.023.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 32)